(Penny:)Leonard, what time does
your mom's plane get in?
(Leonard:)I don't know--
some time tomorrow morning.
(Penny:)Don't you want
to know for sure?
(Leonard:)No need to. As soon as she flies
into California airspace,
(Leonard:)I'll feel a disturbance
in the Force.
(Amy:)It's so nice
both of your moms are coming in
(Amy:)to see you guys get an award.
(Sheldon:)Well, my mother's been there
for every honor I've won
(Sheldon:)since I beat out my twin sister
for the "did it
on the potty" trophy.
(Sheldon:)How does this look?
(Penny:)Aw, it's so nice.
She's gonna love it.
(Amy:)Sure, his mom gets roses.
(Amy:)When I want them,
they're a "bouquet of
severed plant genitals."
(Sheldon:)You act like I didn't get you
(Sheldon:)that mushroom log
on Valentine's Day.
(Amy:)He's right.
(Amy:)Roses die, but a moist rotting
log will pump out mushrooms
(Amy:)for two or three magical years.
(Penny:)You know,
your mom's never been
(Penny:)too thrilled
with our relationship.
(Penny:)Maybe I should get her something
so she warms up to me.
(Leonard:)If you could run
out and get a PhD,
(Leonard:)that might make
her like you.
(Penny:)Really?
It didn't work for you.
(Amy:)Do you think
the moms will get along?
(Leonard:)Uh, I don't know.
They're pretty different.
(Sheldon:)Maybe they'll be best friends.
(Sheldon:)One of them is brilliant,
one is sweet and simple.
(Sheldon:)Sound familiar?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪